{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Stamped or Colored Concrete Wall Pros","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"__cache./api/resource/task/40198/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40198,"taskName":"Stamped or Colored Concrete Wall - Install","taskDescription":"Install a Stamped or Colored Concrete Wall","xmTaskDescriptor":"Stamped or Colored Concrete Wall Pros","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":5217,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Stamped Colored Concrete block masonry","textMessagingName":"Stamp Cncrt Wall","rolloverLongDesc":"Techniques can be used over old \u0026 new concrete. Specialty coatings \u0026 techniques that include stamping, selectively masking \u0026/or dying are used to create an attractive \"pebbly\" or simulated brick or stone look. Aesthetic effects can be dramatic. Includes application of a basic, non-decorative resurfacing product.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes exposed aggregate, simulated brick etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Stamped or Colored Concrete Wall.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Paint a Concrete Wall \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Stamped or Colored Concrete Walls","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Stamped or Colored Concrete Wall Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Stamped or Colored Concrete Wall - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Stamped or Colored Concrete Wall Project","urlName":"Stamped-or-Colored-Concrete-Wall-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Concrete Wall Painters - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Stamped,Colored,Concrete,block,masonry,pool,mason,buildings,Wall","emcCategoryOid":-12015,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":505,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40198/":{"taskOID":40198,"originalTaskOID":40198,"setID":505,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4477,"questionDisplayText":"Purpose of Wall","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose of the wall?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1859,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Decorative wall","answerDisplayText":"Decorative wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4951,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Protective wall","answerDisplayText":"Protective wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7114,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Length","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How long will the wall be?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10872,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 10 ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 10 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10873,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"10 - 25 ft","answerDisplayText":"10 - 25 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10874,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"25 - 50 ft","answerDisplayText":"25 - 50 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10875,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"50 - 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"50 - 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10876,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Over 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"Over 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7115,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Height","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How high will the wall be?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2 ft","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10878,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 4 ft","answerDisplayText":"3 - 4 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10879,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 6 ft","answerDisplayText":"5 - 6 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10880,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Over 6 ft","answerDisplayText":"Over 6 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4478,"questionDisplayText":"Pattern/Color Choices","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What pattern do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2837,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Granite","answerDisplayText":"Granite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5776,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1466,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cobblestone","answerDisplayText":"Cobblestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3775,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Match a sample","answerDisplayText":"Match a sample I have","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1520,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Complement house/yard","answerDisplayText":"Complement house/yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10885,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Random Stone","answerDisplayText":"Random Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5448,"questionDisplayText":"Additional Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any of the following you need for your project.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5749,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Site preparation (excavation, grading)","answerDisplayText":"Site preparation (excavation, grading)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4348,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Old concrete removal","answerDisplayText":"Old concrete removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2073,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Drainage","answerDisplayText":"Drainage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6921,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Waterproofing","answerDisplayText":"Waterproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4477,"questionDisplayText":"Purpose of Wall","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose of the wall?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1859,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Decorative wall","answerDisplayText":"Decorative wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4951,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Protective wall","answerDisplayText":"Protective wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1859,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Decorative wall","answerDisplayText":"Decorative wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4951,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Protective wall","answerDisplayText":"Protective wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7114,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Length","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How long will the wall be?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10872,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 10 ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 10 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10873,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"10 - 25 ft","answerDisplayText":"10 - 25 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10874,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"25 - 50 ft","answerDisplayText":"25 - 50 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10875,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"50 - 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"50 - 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10876,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Over 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"Over 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10872,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 10 ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 10 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10873,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"10 - 25 ft","answerDisplayText":"10 - 25 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10874,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"25 - 50 ft","answerDisplayText":"25 - 50 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10875,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"50 - 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"50 - 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10876,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Over 100 ft","answerDisplayText":"Over 100 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7115,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Height","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How high will the wall be?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2 ft","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10878,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 4 ft","answerDisplayText":"3 - 4 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10879,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 6 ft","answerDisplayText":"5 - 6 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10880,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Over 6 ft","answerDisplayText":"Over 6 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10877,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 2 ft","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10878,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"3 - 4 ft","answerDisplayText":"3 - 4 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10879,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"5 - 6 ft","answerDisplayText":"5 - 6 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10880,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Over 6 ft","answerDisplayText":"Over 6 ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4478,"questionDisplayText":"Pattern/Color Choices","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What pattern do you want? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2837,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Granite","answerDisplayText":"Granite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5776,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1466,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cobblestone","answerDisplayText":"Cobblestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3775,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Match a sample","answerDisplayText":"Match a sample I have","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1520,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Complement house/yard","answerDisplayText":"Complement house/yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10885,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Random Stone","answerDisplayText":"Random Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2837,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Granite","answerDisplayText":"Granite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5776,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Slate","answerDisplayText":"Slate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1466,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cobblestone","answerDisplayText":"Cobblestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3775,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Match a sample","answerDisplayText":"Match a sample I have","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1520,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Complement house/yard","answerDisplayText":"Complement house/yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10885,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Random Stone","answerDisplayText":"Random Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5448,"questionDisplayText":"Additional Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any of the following you need for your project.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5749,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Site preparation (excavation, grading)","answerDisplayText":"Site preparation (excavation, grading)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4348,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Old concrete removal","answerDisplayText":"Old concrete removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2073,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Drainage","answerDisplayText":"Drainage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6921,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Waterproofing","answerDisplayText":"Waterproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5749,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Site preparation (excavation, grading)","answerDisplayText":"Site preparation (excavation, grading)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4348,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Old concrete removal","answerDisplayText":"Old concrete removal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2073,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Drainage","answerDisplayText":"Drainage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6921,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Waterproofing","answerDisplayText":"Waterproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true}